{
    "subject": "resource/Ian_Bruce_Ferguson",
    "predicate": "property/serviceyears",
    "object": "1939",
    "human_readable": "Ian Bruce Ferguson served from 1939.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8888064622879028,
            "question": "From what year did Ian Bruce Ferguson serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7937610149383545,
            "question": "What role did Ian Bruce Ferguson serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7631303668022156,
            "question": "Who is Ian Bruce Ferguson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6300013661384583,
            "question": "Who else served alongside Ian Bruce Ferguson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.54730224609375,
            "question": "What was the context of Ian Bruce Ferguson's service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.530549168586731,
            "question": "How long did Ian Bruce Ferguson serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4683311879634857,
            "question": "What were the responsibilities of Ian Bruce Ferguson's role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4199216365814209,
            "question": "Was there a specific event or reason for Ian Bruce Ferguson's service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41367125511169434,
            "question": "What impact did Ian Bruce Ferguson's service have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3481711745262146,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Ian Bruce Ferguson's service?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ian Bruce Ferguson served from 1939.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4759_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Ian Bruce Ferguson's service have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4759_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was there a specific event or reason for Ian Bruce Ferguson's service?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4759_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the responsibilities of Ian Bruce Ferguson's role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4759_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4759_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Ian Bruce Ferguson enlisted in the Australian Imperial Force on November 3, 1939 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4759/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt). Therefore, it can be inferred that he served from at least 1939."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Ian Bruce Ferguson served from 1939.\" Specifically, it mentions that on 3 November 1939, he enlisted in the Australian Imperial Force at the start of World War II."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}